getrevue.co 2018-10-05

# Revue - An editorial newsletter tool for writers and publishers.

Revue Holding B.V. ("Revue"; "we"), situated in The Netherlands, provides services to our website visitors ("you"). Our services include activities relating to providing a tool that allows writers and publishers to create and send out newsletters, as well as other services ("the Services"). We process personal data during the undertaking of these Services.

Revue deems careful handling of personal data to be paramount. Personal data is carefully processed and secured. When processing, we adhere to the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation (the “Rules"). This Privacy Statement relates to personal information collected by, or under the control of Revue, in accordance with the Rules.

In this Privacy Statement, we summarise what personal data we collect and use and for what purpose. We advise you to read our Privacy Statement carefully. This Privacy Statement applies to our website, https://www.getrevue.co/; related sites; and communications.

You can find the privacy statement relating to the Revue platform here.

_This Privacy Statement was last altered on the 24th May 2018._

### Use of Personal Data

By using our Services, you may share your personal data with us. We exclusively collect and use the personal data that is directly provided by you, or your organisation. Revue will not use your personal data for other purposes than for which you, or your organisation, have given us permission beforehand.

### Types of Data Collected

When using our Services, we may collect the following Information about you:

  * Personal identification data: name, surname;
  * Contact information data: email;
  * Other provided data: IP address, social media accounts, feedback and other communication.

### Purposes of Processing

Personal data is generally processed by Revue for the following purposes:

  * Logging in and verifying/authenticating users of the Service;
  * Communication between Revue and website visitors;
  * Monitoring and auditing the Service;
  * Analysing statistics and optimising the Service.

We collect your personal data based on legitimate business interests, or consent. If the processing is based on consent, it can be withdrawn at any time.

### Data Storage 

In principle, we only keep your data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes described in this Privacy Statement, for which your data have been collected. As a general rule, we store the data our website visitors for 12 months.

### Your Rights

You have the right to request access to the information we have about you. You can do this by contacting us directly. We will make sure to provide you with a copy of the data we process about you in a machine-readable format. We may need to verify your identity to comply with your request.

If you believe that the information we have about you is incorrect, you can contact us, so we can update the information to ensure it is accurate. You also have the right to object to certain data processing operations, such as direct marketing. If at any point you wish for us to delete information about you, you can communicate it to us.

You can contact us at any time with these requests and we will respond in a timely manner applicable with the Rules. If you are unsatisfied with the reply received from us, you may then refer your complaint to the relevant supervisory authority.

### Provision to Third Parties

Your personal data may sometimes be shared with third parties. In principle, we will not provide the data you have provided us to other parties if you have not given us permission to do so, unless this is required by the law.

### Data Transfers

For the fulfilment of the purposes mentioned in this Privacy Statement, your data may be transferred outside the European Economic Area. Whenever this is the case, we make sure that personal data is transferred in a secure manner. For transfers to the US, we ensure that the party is subject to the US-EU Privacy Shield Agreement. For other transfers, your data may be transferred to countries recognized by the European Commission as providing an adequate level of data protection.

### Cookies and Analytics

On our website, we make use of functional cookies. These cookies are saved for the duration of the (browser) session. Additionally, when you use our service, your IP address is automatically saved in the log files of our web server. This is necessary to allow us to properly manage and secure the Services. We do not use your IP address to follow and register your behaviour online. Normally, we are not able to link your IP address to your name, address or other identifying information, except when you actively provide us with such information and continue to make use of the same IP address. You can always refuse the cookies.

User data that you provide may be kept for making statistical analyses, including via Google Analytics. These statistics are used to optimise our Services. Wherever possible, we make this data pseudonymized.

### Security

We take security measures in order to limit misuse of and unauthorised access to personal data. In particular, we take the following measures:

  * Logical access control, use of passwords and possibly a second factor;
  * Encryption of data;
  * Pseudonymising data;
  * Securing data during the exchange of it, making use of the HTTPS protocol;
  * Purpose-bound access limitations;
  * Control of acknowledged authorisations.

### Third Party Websites

This statement does not apply to third party websites that are visited from our Service through links. We cannot guarantee that these third parties will handle your personal data safely and reliably. We advise you to read the Privacy Statements of these websites before making use of them.

Revue Holding B.V.   
Europalaan 500-unit O.2.3,   
3526KS Utrecht,   
The Netherlands
